stripshow.com 2008-12-23

# StripShow.com PRIVACY POLICY

********************

---|---  
  
********************

**StripShow.com PRIVACY POLICY**  
---  
We at StripShow.com understand that your privacy is very important to you. That's why we've developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using StripShow.com.  

**Table of Contents**   
A Special Note About Children   
About StripShow.com and Information We Collect   
Our Use of Your Information   
Our Disclosure of Your Information   
Your use of Other Users' Information   
Control of Your Password   
Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information   
Third Party Collections of Information   
Security   
Update/Delete  
  
**1\. A Special Note About Children**  
Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We ask that children not submit information to us.  
  
**2\. About StripShow.com and Information We Collect**  
StripShow.com is an online network which provides you useful tools and communities to build relationships online. StripShow.com basic service is FREE to all qualified members. 

In our online **ANONYMOUS** registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your age and the type of relationship you are looking for. In addition, we collect address, credit card, and bank information only from those who wish to acquire Gold and Silver member privileges. **However, NONE of the personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual.**

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites automatically collect this information. If you choose to post messages in our Advice Columns, chat rooms, or other message areas, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. StripShow.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [Customer Service](http://stripshow.com/p/help.cgi?dcb=stripshow.com&contact=1) to request that we remove this information from our database.  

**3\. Our Use of Your Information**  
We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs. 

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. 

We also send periodic informational updates to our members via email. 

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement.  
  
**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed in aggregate at all. 

In order to maintain a healthy community, StripShow.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.  

**5\. Your use of Other Users' Information**  
**You may not use other user’s information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. **StripShow.com reserves the right to terminate those who misuse other user’s information or who otherwise violate the StripShow.com Terms of Use.****  
  
**6\. Control of Your Password**  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.  
  
**7\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personally identifiable information at StripShow.com including: 

Your email address  
Your city, state, zip code, country  
Your password  
Your profile

Please promptly update your information if it changes by logging in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information. 

Upon your request, we will remove your credit card number and credit card expiration date from our main databases. To make this request, email us at [Customer Service](http://stripshow.com/p/help.cgi?dcb=stripshow.com&contact=1). We will retain in our files information, including credit card information, you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, comply with Credit Card Merchant Banking and Association Agreements, enhance security, reduce fraud, comply with Federal and State Law, and to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement.  

**8\. Third Party Collections of Information**  
Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. While StripShow.com is working closely with our partners to ensure the highest privacy to you, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) .  

**9\. Security**  
StripShow.com has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. StripShow.com uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at StripShow.com work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.  
  
**10\. Update/Delete**  
StripShow.com Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database: 

  * Send an email to [Customer Service](http://stripshow.com/p/help.cgi?dcb=stripshow.com&contact=1)
  * Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile
  * Send a snail mail to StripShow.com at 220 Humboldt Ct, Sunnyvale, CA 94089, USA
  * Call us at (610) 757-1924

Click here to join our free, safe, and exciting community now.   
  
StripShow.com PRIVACY POLICY  
Effective on: (12/22/05)

Top  
  
********************
